

#### CONTACT

- +971569608305
- Farnaz@blockchainfar.com
- https://www.blockchainfar.com
- Dubai, United Arab Emirates

# **PROFILE**

Responsible, reliable, creative, and professional leader. Problem solver, team player, open to share my knowledge.

Specialized in Blockchain & Web 3.0 development.

Cheerful, ambitious and resilient person. I love my job and achieving milestones working with a team.

# **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate Farsi - Native

#### **SKILLS**

Solidity, Web3.js, ethers.js, Moralis, C#, .Net core, ASP.net, Xamarin, SQL Server, Mongo DB, Node.js, RESTFul API, Javascript, React, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Nextjs Google Cloud Platform, Azure GIT, Figma, Architecture design, Agile

# Farnaz Bagheri

# BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bharati Vidyapeeth**

Master of Information Technology 2017 - 2019

# **Savitribai Phule Pune University**

Bachelor's of computer application 2014-2017

# **Kar University**

Chemical & textile engineering 2010 - 2014

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Part Globals | 2022

I create a website to make their sales online and worked with them to generate more sales online. My work makes their website to have 99 users/ day.

# Music Market Place | 2022

I developed Minting for music market places on Polygon and Ethereum blockchain. I developed the platform in react so that users can mint their musics on the web application.

#### NFT Marketplace | 2022

I developed NFT market place contract to manage physical sales by NFT

# Mint My File | 2022

My responsibility on this project as lead software developer was to make sure all the developers have the same approach to take. Also I was responsible for deployment of smart contracts on Polygon and interaction with the smart contract and IPFS in web 3.0



# CONTACT

- +971569608305
- Farnaz@blockchainfar.com
- https://www.blockchainfar.com
- Dubai, United Arab Emirates

# **PROFILE**

Responsible, reliable, creative, and professional leader. Problem solver, team player, open to share my knowledge.

Specialized in Blockchain & Web 3.0 development.

Cheerful, ambitious and resilient person. I love my job and achieving milestones working with a team.

# **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate Farsi - Native

#### **SKILLS**

Solidity, Web3.js, ethers.js, Moralis, C#, .Net core, ASP.net, Xamarin, SQL Server, Mongo DB, Node.js, RESTFul API, Javascript, React, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Nextjs Google Cloud Platform, Azure GIT, Figma, Architecture design, Agile

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# The next millionaire | 2022

I developed and deployed a lottery contract which users can participate in the contracts with 1 ether and can have a chance to win the whole pot.

# Factory Contract | 2022

I worked as a solidity developer on a smart contract that can clone any ERC-20 smart contract and it's data.

#### Demetara | 2019-2022

My responsibility as a lead developer was to make sure all parts of the project will work perfectly. smart contracts developed and deployed by myself to make sure it is working without any bug and there is no bridge in that. I developed the platform with react js for the custom smart contract and presale contract. 3 different contracts developed by myself in this project. One custom contract, custom token contract, and custom presale contract with 2 different platforms. one web app for presale crowd funding and another for inheritance protocol.

# Liwa Motors | 2020 - 2022

I worked as a full stack developer to develop a mobile app using Xamarin with RESTFul API and SQL server as a database.

I also developed the landing page in Reactis

#### **DLK Store | 2019**

As a full-stack developer, I was responsible for the design & development of an E-commerce application for mobile and web with database design and integration to web application

# Cheeball | 2019

I worked as a full-stack developer, responsible for developing web and mobile application of cheeball, an ecommerce with lottery system.

#### Gozareshrang | 2018 - current

I am the founder of gozareshrang, A report generator web application that automates the report generation for car inspectors with more than 10000 reports generated per month.



#### CONTACT

- +971569608305
- Farnaz@blockchainfar.com
- https://www.blockchainfar.com
- Dubai, United Arab Emirates

# **PROFILE**

Responsible, reliable, creative, and professional leader. Problem solver, team player, open to share my knowledge.

Specialized in Blockchain & Web 3.0 development.

Cheerful, ambitious and resilient person. I love my job and achieving milestones working with a team.

# **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate Farsi - Native

#### **SKILLS**

Solidity, Web3.js, ethers.js, Moralis, C#, .Net core, ASP.net, Xamarin, SQL Server, Mongo DB, Node.js, RESTFul API, Javascript, React, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Nextjs Google Cloud Platform, Azure GIT, Figma, Architecture design, Agile

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# CampingPawna | 2016 - 2018

I develop their online sales process and make their whole system online and this helped them to generate more sales by selling online bookings

# Gozareshrang | 2014-2016

i worked on my own application as Gozareshrang windows application to help vehicle showrooms generate their contracts and agreements online.

# RayaZeytoon | 2012-2014

I worked as an application designer to design RayaZeytoon application for online learning. The application used in some of universities.